Psalm
stop reading
Most people
at the cross.
twenty-two
going
Keep
end in a
doesn't
it
grave.
stay
doesn't
But the cry
forsaken.
Later,
turns
psalm
the
moves from
voice
the same
to praise:
anguish
name
thy
"I will declare
brethren:
my
unto
of the
midst
in the
thee."
will I praise
congregation
voice?
praising
is that
Who
opening line
takes that
Hebrews
and puts
word
word for
of
mouth
it in the
Christ.
risen
the
turn is Jesus,
psalm's
The
side
far
alive on the
cross.
of the
He calls
what
And hear
us.
"not
says He is
Hebrews
them brethren"
call
ashamed to
brothers.
Family.
who cried
Jesus
The same
lives
now
out forsaken
is
Christ
and the risen
His
to call
not ashamed
brethren.
own
you into
calling
He is
family.
that